Petru Coniuc

Frontend Developer

Experienced Middle Frontend Developer with 3 years of experience adept in all stages of advanced web development. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.



Employment History

Frontend Developer at ChessClub, Remote

JANUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

- Translated designs and wire-frames into high-quality code
- Designed and developed new custom reusable components to meet project requirements
- Collaborating with front-end and back-end teams during development process
- · Adapted the project to different devices
- Resolved many tasks using YouTrack issues tracking system

Backend Developer at Grade Arc, Remote

JUNE 2021 – DECEMBER 2021

- · Planned and created RESTful web services
- Integrated testing with Mocha/Chai
- Reviewed codebase and resolved validity and performance issues
- · Collaborated with other members
- Implemented features and resolved tasks using Jira as issues tracking system
- · Documented endpoints

Frontend Developer at Topship, Remote

MARCH 2022 - AUGUST 2022

- · Removed code vulnerabilities
- Collaborated with front-end and back-end teams during development process
- Fixed major bugs
- Implemented features and resolved tasks using Trello as issues tracking system
- Integrated PayPal and Stripe payment services

Software Developer at Pantelwar, Remote

MAY 2022

- Collaborated with front-end and back-end teams during development process
- Implemented features and resolved tasks using Trello as issues tracking
- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers.

Details

Edinet, Moldova, Republic of +37369763951

aihara-sama@mail.ru

Links

<u>Linkedin</u> Github

Skills

JavaScript
Typescript
React
Redux
NextJS
Bootstrap
jQuery
Mui
Cypress
Jest
Mocha/Chai

Node.js



- Utilized the latest software development tools, techniques, and approaches.
- Translated designs and wire-frames into high-quality code
- Started and independently maintained a production-level project

Education

Computer technical support operator at Professional school no. 9, Chişinău

SEPTEMBER 2016 – MAY 2018

NestJS	
ExpressJS	
MongoDB	
MySQL	
Sequelize	
TypeORM	
Mongoose	
Git	
Sockets	
GraphQL	
CI/CD	

Languages

Ensglish			
Moldavia	an; №	1old	ovar
Russian			

Hobbies

Studying chemistry, physics, engineering, etc..

